<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zype Dev Portal</title>
    <description>This is the devloper portal for Zype Media. Zype is Revenue and Reach Magic for Online Video. We help content owners deliver fully branded video experiences.
</description>
    <link>http://dev.zype.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://dev.zype.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 12:10:17 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 12:10:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Importing a YouTube Channel to the Zype Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With the Zype Platform, you can import all of the videos within a YouTube Channel.
This tutorial will go over the three steps to importing all the videos within a Youtube
Channel to your Zype video library.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the Video Source page in the Zype Platform, click on new YouTube Video Source&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/JoQNGol.png&quot; alt=&quot;youtube video sources&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add a new Youtube Video Source you need to input your YouTube Channel ID. Input
your YouTube Channel ID and click save changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/n8Qa0E0.png&quot; alt=&quot;youtube video source new&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Need help finding the YouTube Channel ID? &lt;a href=&quot;/posts/2014/11/04/finding-youtube-channel-id/&quot;&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; for
our tutorial on finding the Channel ID.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you click save changes, the Zype Platform will import the YouTube videos in the
channel supplied. You will need to add those videos to your Zype video library from
the import video screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/yU2X3UU.png&quot; alt=&quot;import youtube video&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The video imports that you add will now be a part of your Zype video library.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 05:57:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/05/importing-youtube-channel-to-zype</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/05/importing-youtube-channel-to-zype</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding a YouTube Channel ID</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;To import a YouTube Channel into the Zype Platform, you need to have its Channel ID.
This ID can be tricky to find because the Channel ID and User ID are very similar.
Below are the options and steps to finding a YouTube Channel ID
to input into the Zype Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finding your YouTube Channel ID:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. Log into your YouTube account and visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/account_advanced&quot;&gt;advanced account settings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2. Your Channel ID can be found in your Account Information&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/fh76FMH.png&quot; alt=&quot;channel id instructions&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finding an additional YouTube Channel ID:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YouTube is in the process of moving from videos belonging to Users to videos
belonging to Channels. Because of this migration, it is tricky to get your Channel ID because often, YouTube treats User and Channel as the same thing. It is important to make sure that you are getting the Channel ID and not the User ID for the Zype Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. Visit a YouTube video that is in the Channel you want and click on the channel name
below the Video Player.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/28no7XC.png&quot; alt=&quot;youtube video&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2. You will be taken to the Channel Page. The Channel ID is at the end of the URL.
For example, for Last Week Tonight with John Oliver, the channel ID is UC3XTzVzaHQEd30rQbuvCtTQ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/bisJffi.png&quot; alt=&quot;youtube channel page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Common Mistakes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since YouTube is changing from User to Channel Pages, the User Page looks very similar
to the Channel Page. The URL for the User Page has &lt;strong&gt;/user/&lt;/strong&gt; in it, not &lt;strong&gt;/channel/&lt;/strong&gt;. If
you find yourself on the User Page instead of the Channel Page, click on a video in the User
Page and repeat the steps for finding an additional YouTube Channel ID above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Ef8qcgA.png&quot; alt=&quot;youtube user page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 05:57:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/04/finding-youtube-channel-id</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/04/finding-youtube-channel-id</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Russian Doll Caching in Rails 4</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While developing, we always keep the user experience in mind and one of the most important things for a content heavy application
is load times. In rails, this usually comes down to how quickly you can render the requested view. Today I want to take a quick look
at how to nest caching statements in rails 4 for maximum effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-russian-doll-caching&quot;&gt;What is Russian doll caching?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Russian-doll caching is a convention used in Rails 4 to improve the load time of your views. It involves using nested fragment caching statements so that only the page content that has changed since the last request needs to be regenerated. All the other elements of the page are simply read from their still-valid caches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s an example of some nested fragment caching statements in a view for a gallery of videos:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/cCQLi4g.png&quot; alt=&quot;nested cache statements&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each level of nesting ensures that you only pay to read the caches of the content nested above it, not regenerate it, when the content nested below it changes. This has a reverse cascading effect, so the more strategic you can be with your caching statements, the less time you’ll spend trying to re-render the page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;where-should-i-start-adding-russian-doll-caching&quot;&gt;Where should I start adding Russian doll caching?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The parts of your app that are viewed most often will likely be your best targets for russian doll caching. Anywhere that you’re displaying a mix of dynamic and static content is also a good target because you can eliminate the need to reload the entire page when only a portion of the content has changed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a look at your views and see if you can compartmentalize them based on content, this will be easier if you’re already using partials in the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a visual example of the nested nature of the caching statements from the code above:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/8PxC8mg.png&quot; alt=&quot;seeing the nests in your view&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;further-reading&quot;&gt;Further reading&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read up about cache expiration and best practices from DHH himself:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://signalvnoise.com/posts/3112-how-basecamp-next-got-to-be-so-damn-fast-without-using-much-client-side-ui&quot;&gt;Here &lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://signalvnoise.com/posts/3113-how-key-based-cache-expiration-works&quot;&gt;- and here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 06:57:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/24/russian-doll-caching</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/24/russian-doll-caching</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Adding a playlist of related videos</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Let’s say you’ve already got some video content on your zype destination site, but now you’d like to recommend
additional content based on what your users are watching. The solution we’ve implemented is called related videos.
In this post, we’ll be covering how to create a playlist of related videos that are recommended to a viewer
based on what the video they’re watching. Here’s an example of the finished product:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/QGhFTT1.png&quot; alt=&quot;related playlist&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The related videos section is automatically created for each video on your site, but if you’d like to be more
specific about which videos are displayed there, follow along as we set up a playlist of related videos.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-do-i-set-up-a-playlist-of-related-videos&quot;&gt;How do I set up a playlist of related videos?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Setting up the playlist can be done from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com/&quot;&gt;admin portal&lt;/a&gt;. Navigate to the playlist
section on the sidebar and and click “New Playlist”. Follow through the menu and create a playlist (make sure it’s active!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/2yzWH9X.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlist navigation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-can-i-choose-which-videos-are-shown-in-the-playlist&quot;&gt;How can I choose which videos are shown in the playlist?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an easy one. Use the “Add Videos” button to select which videos will appear under the related videos section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/nKIFmTP.png&quot; alt=&quot;add videos navigation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-can-i-choose-which-videos-display-the-playlist&quot;&gt;How can I choose which videos display the playlist?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Choosing the videos that will have your playlist displayed is done through the playlist edit screen. You can get there
quickly by clicking on the name of your playlist here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/XSvwXVR.png&quot; alt=&quot;edit your playlist&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use our multiselector to search for the videos you want and click on them to move them into selected videos.
Click “Save Changes” when you’re done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/xE9fM8n.png&quot; alt=&quot;choose related videos&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lets-confirm&quot;&gt;Let’s confirm&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should take a second and make sure everything’s going according to plan. Go to your site and view a video
that you added to selected videos in the previous step. Below the video, under the section “Related Videos”,
you should see the playlist you just created and the first few videos you added. You can also update any of your
current playlists to act as a playlist of related videos by following these same steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Check our &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/10/adding-zype-to-rails/&quot;&gt;previous post&lt;/a&gt;
on how to set up your Rails App with the Zype Gem!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2014 02:37:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/23/adding-a-playlist-of-related-videos</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/23/adding-a-playlist-of-related-videos</guid>
        
        
        <category>videos</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Checking your DPT request logs</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In a previous post, we covered how to use Zype’s Dynamic Player Technology (DPT).
In this post, we’ll be covering how to use the DPT logs to see what requests are being made for your video content.
For example, let’s say you’ve uploaded a batch of new videos and after the first 30 days, you’d like to get an idea
of who’s viewing your content and what times of the day are most popular for viewing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;where-can-i-find-my-logs&quot;&gt;Where can I find my logs?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you’ve uploaded some video content to the Zype platform, log in through the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com/&quot;&gt;admin portal&lt;/a&gt;
and navigate to the logs section under the settings dropdown menu. In this post, we’ll cover the request logs,
so feel free to click on that link once you see the logs menu.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/werWhEG.png&quot; alt=&quot;dpt logs navigation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-type-of-information-can-i-see-in-my-request-logs&quot;&gt;What type of information can I see in my request logs?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The request logs screen shows you lots of information about the requests made to view your videos.
Here are the most pertinent pieces of information:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Data&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Description&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Video&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The video that was requested&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;IP Address&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The IP address of the requester&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Country&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The country the request was made from&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Device&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The device the request was made from&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Player&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The player that served the video&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Provider&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The provider of the content&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Revenue Model&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The revenue model of the viewer&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Status&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The status of the request&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Created&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;The date and time the request was created&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Y8DzoV9.png&quot; alt=&quot;dpt logs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-can-i-search-the-request-logs-data&quot;&gt;How can I search the request logs data?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The request logs screen gives you a snapshot of the most recent requests by default.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorting the request logs is easy: use the four drop down menus to select your search parameters
and then click on the search button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/XgruOt5.png&quot; alt=&quot;searching logs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Check our &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/10/adding-zype-to-rails/&quot;&gt;previous post&lt;/a&gt;
on how to set up your Rails App with the Zype Gem!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 05:07:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/20/checking-player-request-logs</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/20/checking-player-request-logs</guid>
        
        
        <category>dpt</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Using Zype&#39;s Dynamic Player Technology (DPT)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Zype’s DPT allows you to create player rules based on geography and device.
For example, you could declare that end users will receive the Hulu Player if he
or she is accessing your video via desktop in the United States or the Zype Player
if he or she is accessing your video via desktop in Australia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-you-need-to-start&quot;&gt;What you need to start&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need to have a video collection on the Zype Platform from the video sources
that you want to create player rules for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. Make sure you have imported your videos into your &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/video_imports&quot;&gt;video catalogue&lt;/a&gt;
on the Zype Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/XmeaBMa.png&quot; alt=&quot;video imports&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-you-need-to-do-in-the-zype-platform&quot;&gt;What you need to do in the Zype Platform&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. Visit the &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/player_rules&quot;&gt;Player Rule Page&lt;/a&gt; and click on New Player Rule&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/qDK0aoL.png&quot; alt=&quot;player rules&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2. Complete the Player Rules Form. You will need to know the countries and devices you want for your rule.
Based on countries and devices, you will be given player options that can be served to the end user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/nxcYd0K.png&quot; alt=&quot;player rule form&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;using-the-player-api&quot;&gt;Using the Player API&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. Once you have set up your video catalogue in the Zype Platform and you have created your player rules, you are ready to use the Zype Player API!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2. You can find your player key and api key using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/site/api&quot;&gt;Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/V7UoP3i.png?1&quot; alt=&quot;site keys&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3a. To make the API call to get the appropriate player&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;GET&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;http&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;sr&quot;&gt;//&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;api&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;video_id&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;player&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;api_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;api_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;player_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;player_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3b. To use the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/edla/zype-cli&quot;&gt;Zype Ruby Gem&lt;/a&gt; to get the appropriate player&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype_cli&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Client&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@video&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype_cli&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;find&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;params&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:video_id&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@player&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@video&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;player&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;player_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;params&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:player_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Check our &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/10/adding-zype-to-rails/&quot;&gt;previous post&lt;/a&gt;
on how to set up your Rails App with the Zype Gem!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 11:53:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/17/dpt-from-scratch</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/17/dpt-from-scratch</guid>
        
        
        <category>dpt</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Filter Playlists by a Category in a Rails App</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;To organize your playlists using the Zype Platform, you can assign categories to
your playlists and filter your playlists based on a category and its value.
In this tutorial, I will walk through how to query for all the playlists that have
a category named ‘zone’ and a value of ‘home.’ At Zype, we use this
strategy to get all the playlists that we want to be displayed on the home page or zone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1: Go to admin.zype.com/categories and click the create new category button&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/nweBnRo.png&quot; alt=&quot;new category&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2: Fill out the category title and category values. You can have multiple
values (and you can always go back and edit these category values!)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/DmREstQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;new category&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3: Create a playlist and assign it the Zone Category of home&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/0algUs9.png&quot; alt=&quot;new category&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4: In your Rails App, query for playlists that have the category zone value of home.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@playlists&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;playlists&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;zone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;home&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 11:53:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/13/playlists-and-categories</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/13/playlists-and-categories</guid>
        
        
        <category>rails</category>
        
        <category>ruby</category>
        
        <category>playlists</category>
        
        <category>categories</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Adding Zype to a Rails Application</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At Zype, we use our &lt;a href=&quot;link: https://github.com/edla/zype-cli&quot;&gt;Zype Gem&lt;/a&gt; to
build fully branded video experiences on the web. Below is a step-by-step
guide for how to integrate the Zype Gem into a Rails App.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. Add the Zype Gem to your Gemfile and bundle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;gem&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;zype&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:git&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;git://github.com/edla/zype-cli.git&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2. Add your Zype Configurations to the initializers directory&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# Create a new file config/initializers/zype.rb&lt;/span&gt;

  &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;configure&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;do&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;|&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;config&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;|&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;config&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;api_key&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;api_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;config&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;host&lt;/span&gt;    &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;api.zype.com&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;config&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;port&lt;/span&gt;    &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;80&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;config&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;use_ssl&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;false&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can find your api key from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com/site/api&quot;&gt;Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3. Add the following javascript to your layout.html.erb to be able to power the appropriate player javascript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot; data-lang=&quot;html&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;script &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;type=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;src=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;http://api.zype.com/player.js&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;script &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;type=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;player_key&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;player_key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;};&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can find your player key from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com/site/api&quot;&gt;Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4. Create a new instance of your Zype Client so that you can query the Zype Platform
to get your videos, playlists, categories, zobjects, and appropriate video players
from your Rails App.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Client&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5. Some things that you can do with your Zype Client that could be useful for a web app:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get all your videos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get a specific video&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;find&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;params&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:video_id&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Change pagination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;all&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;per_page&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;500&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pagination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;all&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;page&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;per_page&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;50&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sort (ex. sort by video title)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;all&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;sort&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;‘&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;order&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;‘&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;asc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Query by zobject type (example: genre)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;zobjects&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;all&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;‘&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;zobject_name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{})&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Query videos by category (example genre)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;all&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;category&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;genre&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;‘&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Comedy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;})&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get the player for a video&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@video&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;find&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;params&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:video_id&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@player&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@video&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;player&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;player_opts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6. Display the video player in your HTML view&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-erb&quot; data-lang=&quot;erb&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;%=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;vi&quot;&gt;@player&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;body&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;html_safe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;cp&quot;&gt;%&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;x&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2014 11:53:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/10/adding-zype-to-rails</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/10/10/adding-zype-to-rails</guid>
        
        
        <category>rails</category>
        
        <category>ruby</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
