<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zype Dev Portal</title>
    <description>This is the devloper portal for Zype Media. Zype is Revenue and Reach Magic for Online Video. We help content owners deliver fully branded video experiences.
</description>
    <link>http://dev.zype.com//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://dev.zype.com//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 14:07:13 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 14:07:13 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Organizing your videos for your Roku Channel</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Now that you have set up your Roku Channel and have tested the private channel, you
can organize how the videos are displayed on your Roku Channel. To do this,
you will need to create a featured playlist and a featured category on the Zype Platform. The first row
of your Roku Channel displays your featured playlist while the remaining rows iterate
through your the values in your featured category.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Categories,%20Playlists%20and%20Your%20Roku%20App/roku_playlist.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlist and categories&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create your featured playlist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To create your featured playlist, navigate to the Playlists dashboard via the lefthand
menu and click on “New Playlist”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/roku/playlist_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlist 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, fill in the information for the playlist. The title will be what appears as the
name of the video row on your Roku Channel. Make sure that you mark the playlist as active.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/roku/playlist_2.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlist 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, you need to add videos to your playlists. Go to the playlist and click “Add Videos.”
Note, Roku can only play videos that are from Zype or Vimeo Pro. If you want this playlist
to play on Roku, you will need to only add videos that have these video sources. You
can order videos in your playlists by dragging the videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/roku/playlist_2b.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlist 2b&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last, search for the videos that you would like to be included in your playlist. You
can search for the videos by title in the search box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/roku/playlist_3.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlist 3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/roku/playlist_2c.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlist 4&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have a featured playlist, go to your Roku Channel in the Zype Platform and
click on Edit Advanced Settings. In the “Main Configurations” tab, you can select
the featured playlist. Click save changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/roku/update_channel_playlist.png&quot; alt=&quot;category playlist update&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create your featured category&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To create your featured category, navigate to the Category dashboard via the lefthand
menu and click on “New Category”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/roku/category_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;category 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, fill in the information for your category. The values of the category are what get
seen on your Roku. They are displayed in the order that are in the list. Each value
gets its own row on Roku. You can determine whether or not to prepend the category name
to the value in your advanced Roku settings. You can order videos in your category by setting
the episode number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/roku/category_2.png&quot; alt=&quot;category 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you have your category values, you will need to assign these values to each
of your videos. Go to your video and select the metadata tab. Then, check the values
that you want and click save. You can also mass assign categories from the Video Library screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/roku/category_3.png&quot; alt=&quot;category 3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have a featured category, go to your Roku Channel in the Zype Platform and
click on Edit Advanced Settings. In the “Main Configurations” tab, you can select
the featured category, and whether or not to prepend your category name.
Click save changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/roku/update_channel_playlist.png&quot; alt=&quot;category playlist update&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reload your Roku Channel, you should see the first row be your featured playlist and the
remaining rows be the your category values!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 06:37:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/05/11/organizing-videos-for-roku</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/05/11/organizing-videos-for-roku</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Forgot Password</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You can reset your password by going to &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/&quot;&gt;the Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt;
and following the photo tutorial below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/&quot;&gt;the Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt; and click on “Forgot your password.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/password/forgot_password_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;forgot password 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fill in the email that you used to sign up for your Zype account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/password/forgot_password_2.png&quot; alt=&quot;forgot password 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Receive an email from Zype and click on “Change my password.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/password/forgot_password_3.png&quot; alt=&quot;forgot password 3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter new password and confirm your new password&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/password/forgot_password_4.png&quot; alt=&quot;forgot password 4&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 06:37:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/04/09/forgot-password</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/04/09/forgot-password</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Change Video Thumbnails</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When you upload a video to the Zype Platform, Zype will create thumbnails for your video.
To change your the thumbnail for your video, follow the steps below. Note, this is only
to change your thumbnail from a video uploaded directly to the Zype Platform. It does not apply to
thumbnails from an external data source like YouTube or Vimeo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/thumbnails/thumbnails_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;thumbnail 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From your video library, click on the video that you want to change the thumbnail
for and click on the “Thumbnails” tab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/thumbnails/thumbnails_2.png&quot; alt=&quot;thumbnail 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Select the thumbnail that you want. The thumbnail will automatically be updated!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 06:37:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/04/09/change-thumbnails</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/04/09/change-thumbnails</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Importing Videos from a Third Party Source</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve made it easier to import your videos from third party sources like YouTube, Vimeo, or Hulu
to your video library! Now, the default option is to automatically add all video imports to your
video library as new videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1: Add your video source and make sure that add videos is turned on&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/video_sources/add_source.png&quot; alt=&quot;add video source&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2: Navigate to your Video Library, you should see new videos from your video source that
are active! Note, videos will be added to your video library as they become available&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/video_sources/video_library.png&quot; alt=&quot;video library&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced Importing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you do not want to automatically import all of the videos from a video source to your video
library or if you want to merge your video imports to videos preexisting in your library, you can
turn add video ‘off’ when you create a video source and use the “Advanced Video Importing”
option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/video_sources/add_source_not_auto.png&quot; alt=&quot;add video source not-auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, navigate to the video imports screen and click on the add button for the videos that you
want to add to your video library or the merge button if you want to merge your video imports to
preexisting videos in your video library.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/video_sources/advanced_video_imports.png&quot; alt=&quot;advanced video importing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 05:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/15/importing-videos-from-third-party-source</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/15/importing-videos-from-third-party-source</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bulk Video Importing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;To bulk add video imports to your video library, check the videos that you want to add and click
the button “Add to Library.” This will automatically add new videos to your video library. If you
would like to merge videos into preexisting videos in your video library, you will need to click
the merge chain for each video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/video_imports/bulk_add.png&quot; alt=&quot;add to library&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To bulk remove video imports from your video library, check the videos that you want to remove
and click the button “Remove from Library.” Note, this does not delete the video, it only removes
the chosen video import data source from your video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/video_imports/bulk_remove.png&quot; alt=&quot;remove from library&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 05:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/15/bulk-video-importing</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/15/bulk-video-importing</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Publishing a Roku Channel on the Zype Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We have simplified the process of publishing a Roku Channel from the Zype Platform.
The process now has three parts. First, you need to set up your channel.
Then, Zype will build your Channel for you or you can
&lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2015/02/13/self-publish-roku/&quot;&gt;self-publish your Channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1: Set Up Your Video Library and Channel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, you will need to upload and transcode videos onto the Zype Platform.
Currently, Roku Channels only support videos with a Zype video source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Uploading Videos to the Zype Platform from the Web/upload_video_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;upload and transcode&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, you will need to set up your Roku Channel. Navigate to the Video Apps page&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/dashboard_to_video_app.png&quot; alt=&quot;video apps page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click on Roku to set up a new Roku Channel for publishing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/set_up_roku_app.png&quot; alt=&quot;Roku publishing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set up your Roku Channel by supplying a title, subtitle, a channel image, and
select a channel template. Zype will create multiple images from your one supplied
channel image including your channel logo, poster art, and loading screen.
It is suggested to have a 640 px by 480 px PNG image because the image will be used
in many different sizes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/set_up_roku_screen.png&quot; alt=&quot;roku set up&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2: Zype Builds Your Roku Channel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you set up your Channel, Zype will bundle the necessary images and prepare the
code for your Roku Channel. All you have to do is wait a couple of minutes!
The page will automatically refresh once your Channel is ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/roku_bundling.png&quot; alt=&quot;roku bundling&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3: Publish Channel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can choose to either self-publish or have Zype publish your Roku Channel for you.
If you choose to self publish &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2015/02/13/self-publish-roku/&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;
to read our guide to self publish your Roku Channel.
If you choose to have Zype publish your channel, you will be sent to a checkout
page to redeem your publishing package or pay for a publishing package.
Once you checkout, a member of the Zype team will package, QA, and submit your
Roku Channel to the Roku Channel Store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/roku_publishing.png&quot; alt=&quot;roku publishing options&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Typically, once your Roku Channel is submitted to the Roku Channel Store, it takes
3-4 weeks to get to the front of the QA queue and then another 1-2 weeks for approval.
You should expect to wait atleast 4-6 weeks for your Roku Channel to be available
on the Roku Channel Store. If you would like to immediately share your Roku Channel,
you can create a private Roku Channel that can be shared immediately via url.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4: Edit Channel Settings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The majority of settings for your Roku Channel are configured at run-time.
Thus, you can edit Channel settings such as your featured playlist, your logos and
themes without having to re-publish. &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2015/02/13/roku-advanced-settings/&quot;&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt;
to read how to edit your Roku Channel.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 05:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/13/zype-publish-roku</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/13/zype-publish-roku</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Self Publishing a Roku Channel on the Zype Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Before being ready to self-publish, you will need to set up your Roku Channel on the Zype
Platform. &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2015/02/13/zype-publish-roku&quot;&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to read up on
how to set up your Roku Channel for publishing.
To self-publish your Roku Channel, you will need to have a Roku device and be
comfortable using the terminal. This tutorial is focused for those users who are
on Mac or linux. If you are on Windows, you can follow along with the tutorial,
but you will need to use the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sdkdocs.roku.com/display/sdkdoc/Eclipse+Plugin+Guide&quot;&gt;Eclipse BrightScript plug-in to package your Roku Channel&lt;/a&gt; (step 2).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1: Enable Roku Development Mode on Your Box&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need to enable Roku Development Mode on your Roku device. Read through the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sdkdocs.roku.com/display/sdkdoc/Developer+Guide#DeveloperGuide-70LoadingandRunningyourApplicationWalkthrough&quot;&gt;Roku
Documentation&lt;/a&gt;
on how to load and run your Roku Channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please store your ROKU_DEV_TARGET (the IP address
of your Roku) and DEVPASSWORD (you will get to choose this when you set up your Roku Developer Device). You will need both of these to side load
your Roku Channel into your Roku device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2: Unzip your bundled channel and test out locally (Mac/Linux)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zype will email you a bundled channel zip that contains the BrightScript code for your Roku Channel. You will need to unzip your channel and, in your terminal, navigate to the Roku code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, open up app.mk in your text editor of choice and change the ROKU_DEV_TARGET
and DEVPASSWORD to match your Roku device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/replace_appmk_vars.png&quot; alt=&quot;app.mk replacement&quot; /&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, run make install inside the Roku Channel directory in your terminal to side load your Roku Channel to your Roku device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/make_install.png&quot; alt=&quot;make install&quot; /&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the command is successful, your Roku Channel will load automatically to your Roku Device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3: Package Your Roku Channel for Publishing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need to key your Roku Channel using your Roku device.
Please read the official &lt;a href=&quot;http://sdkdocs.roku.com/display/sdkdoc/Channel+Packaging+And+Publishing#ChannelPackagingAndPublishing-30PackagingYourApplication&quot;&gt;Roku
documentation&lt;/a&gt;
on how to generate your key and key your device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4: Submit Your Roku Channel to the Roku Channel Store&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you have a packaged Roku Channel, you will need to submit your Roku Channel to the Roku Channel Store. You can choose to either publish
a private channel or a public channel. A private channel will be published right away, but is not searchable via the Roku Channel Store. You will
be given a Channel URL that you can share to others to add your private channel. To publish a public channel, you will added to the Roku
Publishing Queue for Roku QA. Based on high demand, it can take anywhere from 2 to 3 months to
get approved by Roku into the Roku Channel Store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;a href=&quot;https://owner.roku.com/Developer/Apps&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to submit your Roku Channel!
You will have to be logged into your Roku Developer Account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please feel free to reach out to Zype using the question box &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/&quot;&gt;in the lower left hand corner&lt;/a&gt;
if you have any questions or would like Zype to publish your Roku Channel for you!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 05:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/13/self-publish-roku</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/13/self-publish-roku</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Advanced Settings for Your Roku Channel</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Selecting a Channel Template and uploading a Channel Image takes most of the hard
work out of branding your Roku Channel. However, if you want to further specialize
your Roku Channel, you can click on Edit Advanced Settings for your Roku Channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/roku_advanced_settings_btn.png&quot; alt=&quot;advanced settings btn&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Advanced Settings have a lot of options! The highest impact advanced settings
that you can change are in the Main Configurations Tab and the Image Configurations Tab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, in the Main Configurations, you can change which playlist is to
be featured at the top of your Roku Channel and you can change the category to
iterate through for the rest of your Roku Channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/main_configs.png&quot; alt=&quot;main configs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the Image Configurations, you can change the run time images such as your logo, slice images,
and grid images. These images are grabbed through the Zype API each time your Roku
Channel gets loaded, so you can upload a new image and refresh your Roku Channel to see
it being changed in real time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/image_configs.png&quot; alt=&quot;image configs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also change your Channel Build Details. Note, however, that if you change
images in your Channel Build Details like your store or focus image, you will
need to resubmit your Channel to the Roku Channel Store.
If you have not yet submitted your Roku Channel, you will need to grab a new bundle of your Roku Channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Publishing Your Roku App/build_configs.png&quot; alt=&quot;image configs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 05:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/13/roku-advanced-settings</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/13/roku-advanced-settings</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Publish an iPhone App from the Zype Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Before we start, lets look at what the end result of what your iPhone App will look like!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/iphone/mockup.png&quot; alt=&quot;iphone preview&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To configure your iPhone App using the Zype Platform, navigate to the Video Apps page and click
on the iPhone logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/iphone/apps_screen.png&quot; alt=&quot;select iphone&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, fill in the App Details. This includes the title, the version number, and the store icon.
The store icon will be the icon that users click to on your iPhone screen to enter your app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/iphone/app_details_screen.png&quot; alt=&quot;app details&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, fill out the Channel Information. The banner image is what appears at the top of your home
screen. The larger banner is for higher quality displays. Check out the mock up of an iPhone App
below to see where the banner gets displayed in the home screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/iphone/channel_screen.png&quot; alt=&quot;channel screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/iphone/mockup-help.png&quot; alt=&quot;banner display&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, add tiles. Tiles are what a user can click on in the app’s home screen to go to the appropriate page. An iPhone app can have up to 9 tiles.
Tiles can include links to Twitter, Facebook, Google+, your blog, your personal website,
favorites, videos, and messages. You can drag the tiles in the editor to change their order on
the iPhone Screen. Check out the mock up tosee where the tiles get displayed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/iphone/tiles_screen.png&quot; alt=&quot;tile screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/iphone/mockup-help.png&quot; alt=&quot;tiles display&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to add a message to your users at this time, you can click on the Message tab
and add a message.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/iphone/message_screen.png&quot; alt=&quot;message screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you are finished, click save changes. You will be redirected to the iPhone App details
screen where you will see a mock up of your channel home screen. You can either
use Zype’s &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;API documentation&lt;/a&gt; to self-publish or have Zype publish
for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/iphone/iphone_show.png&quot; alt=&quot;iphone preview&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 05:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/13/publish-iphone-advanced</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com//posts/2015/02/13/publish-iphone-advanced</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Adding a YouTube Video from a Link</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re happy to announce that the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com&quot;&gt;Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt; now grants you the power to import videos from YouTube simply by copying an pasting a YouTube link into the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com/video_imports&quot;&gt;Video Imports Screen&lt;/a&gt; and click on the “Add a YouTube Video Import” button to get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Adding YouTube Video from a URL/add_video_imports_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;navigate to form&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next step is to copy a URL from YouTube that shows the video you want to add.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Adding YouTube Video from a URL/copy_url.png&quot; alt=&quot;copy url&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paste the URL into the field on this page and click “Add Video Import”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/assets/Adding YouTube Video from a URL/paste_url.png&quot; alt=&quot;paste url&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If everything went according to plan, you should see the video imports screen again, with a new import from the link you provided. If you’re interested in grabbing a bunch of videos from YouTube, you may want to follow our guides under &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/platform_docs/adding_videos/&quot;&gt;Adding Videos.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 21:16:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com//posts/2014/12/25/adding-youtube-embeds</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com//posts/2014/12/25/adding-youtube-embeds</guid>
        
        
        <category>platform</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
