<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zype Dev Portal</title>
    <description>This is the devloper portal for Zype Media. Zype is Revenue and Reach Magic for Online Video. We help content owners deliver fully branded video experiences.
</description>
    <link>http://dev.zype.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://dev.zype.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 18:04:06 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 18:04:06 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sample Rails App using the Zype Platform and API</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We want to make the Zype Platform accessible to as many types of developers as possible. To do this,
we have provided &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/api_docs/intro/&quot;&gt;API documentation&lt;/a&gt; and are happy
to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:contact@zypemedia.com&quot;&gt;talk with you&lt;/a&gt; about creating a turnkey app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a developer, I always like to learn by example, so we have created
a template Rails app to show you what you can do with the Zype Platform using our Ruby Gem and also provide you with a starter template if you want to build off of it for your own web app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We intentionally kept the styling simple and used &lt;a href=&quot;http://getbootstrap.com/&quot;&gt;Bootstrap&lt;/a&gt; if
you would like to use this example as a foundation to your Rails app.
Feel free to clone the repo &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/zype/zype-rails&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. You will
need your Zype API and Player Keys from the Zype Platform. The README has directions
to how you can find your keys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Zype Rails Sample App has the following pages and features.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home Page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The homepage includes all of your playlists, a link in the header to view all videos,
and a search box to search for a specific video. The Playlists can be configured
in the Zype Platform and can be fetched via the Ruby Gem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/XdD1n7n.png&quot; alt=&quot;homepage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Playlist Page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can click on any playlist to view all the videos that belong to that playlist. You can sort
the videos based on release date, name, or popularity. Also note that there are Zype Videos
and YouTube videos in the same player. The Zype Platform and Zype API allows you to
seamlessly combine the two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/uDlDPcK.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlist page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browse all Videos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The browse all videos uses the Ruby Gem to query the Zype API to get all the videos.
When you hover over a video, you will see the description. Feel free to read the &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/api_docs/videos/&quot;&gt;Video API Documentation&lt;/a&gt; to see what other information
gtes returned when you query for the videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ys7ZfD3.png&quot; alt=&quot;browse videos&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video Page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you click on a video’s thumbnail, you get directed to the video’s page. The video’s page
contains the title, description, and video player. The Zype API will deliver the appropriate
player based on where the video source comes from and what Player Rules you set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/EjY7wlU.png&quot; alt=&quot;video page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have questions about implementing our sample Rails app or want to see examples of
other features or in other languages? Feel free to comment below!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 04:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/29/sample-rails-zype</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/29/sample-rails-zype</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Publishing a Roku Channel: Part III - Publishing the Channel</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/develop-roku-app-with-zype-sdk/&quot;&gt;part two&lt;/a&gt; of publishing a Roku Channel, we described how to develop a Roku app using the Zype SDK and running it locally.
In this tutorial, we will walk through how to publish a Private Roku Channel that you can
share immediately with anyone that owns a Roku. If you are interested in publishing a Public Roku Channel, the steps are very similar, just you have to wait for Roku to approve your channel before it can be accessed in the Roku Channel Store. It is recommended that you first publish a private channel, test the channel out to beta users, and then publish the channel publicly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before starting this tutorial, we will assume that you have already tested a Roku App
locally and are a registered Roku developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Log into your Roku developer account and click Manage My Channels&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/K66GKpz.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click add Private Channel. If you want to publish a Public Channel, click add Public Channel.
The steps are the same for private and public channels, except that you will need to
give contact information in case Roku has questions when they are reviewing your app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/GeJiK58.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fill out Channel Properties for your channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/VZDUXsL.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fill our Channel Descriptions for your channel. You will need to have an HD Poster
that is a 290 x 218 JPEG file and an SD Poster that is a 214 x 144 JPEG file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/pFA3aHQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 4&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can optionally upload screenshots of your Roku Channel. Read the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sdkdocs.roku.com/display/sdkdoc/Channel+Packaging+And+Publishing#ChannelPackagingAndPublishing-38GeneratingScreenshotsSincev31onRoku1andv43onRoku2&quot;&gt;Roku documentation&lt;/a&gt; on how to generate a screenshot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/lMtmsak.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 5&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 6&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last, you will need to upload your application package. Follow the instructions from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sdkdocs.roku.com/display/sdkdoc/Channel+Packaging+And+Publishing#ChannelPackagingAndPublishing-30PackagingYourApplication&quot;&gt;Roku documentation&lt;/a&gt; on how to generate a key and then package your channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have downloaded your Roku Channel package, upload the application package and click the “Publish” arrow. You will get an access code url that can be used to download the private
Roku channel on your individual Roku account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/xufsqQC.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 6&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More tutorials in this series:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part I: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/25/create-roku-app-on-zype/&quot;&gt;Creating a Roku Channel using the Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part II: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/develop-roku-app-with-zype-sdk/&quot;&gt;Developing the Roku Channel using the Zype SDK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 04:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/publish-roku-app</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/publish-roku-app</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Publishing a Roku Channel: Part II - Developing Your Roku App Using the Zype SDK</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/25/create-roku-app-on-zype/&quot;&gt;previous tutorial&lt;/a&gt;,
we described how to create a Roku App using the Zype Platform. In this tutorial,
we will walk through how to develop a Roku app using the Zype SDK and testing it locally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To complete this tutorial, we expect that you know how to clone a repo on GitHub. You do
not need to have prior experience with the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sdkdocs.roku.com/display/sdkdoc/BrightScript+Language+Reference&quot;&gt;BrightScript language&lt;/a&gt;
that Roku uses to create Roku Channels, but you should be comfortable with programming because
you will need to update some variables within the cloned app and &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Telnet&quot;&gt;telnet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, you need to have a Roku available to test out your app and a developer account with Roku to publish the app. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.roku.com/developer&quot;&gt;Register here&lt;/a&gt; for a Roku developer account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should have already created a Roku App on the Zype Platform. If you need help
creating a Roku App from the Zype Platform, please read our &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/25/create-roku-app-on-zype/&quot;&gt;previous tutorial&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you have a Roku App created on the Zype Platform, you will need to turn developer mode
on for your Roku. This will allow you to test out your app before you publish it on your local Roku.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To set up your Roku for developer mode, navigate to the home screen of your Roku
and, with your Roku remote control, click the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Home 3x, Up 2x, Right, Left, Right, Left, Right.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On your Roku, you will be prompted to enter a developer password for the Roku device.
Record the password that you enter because it will be used to load your channel in development mode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will also need to record your Roku Player’s IP address. In your Roku, go to
Settings &amp;gt; Network to find it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that your Roku is set up for developer mode and you have recorded your Developer Password
and your Roku Player’s IP address, you are set to grab the Zype Roku SDK from our GitHub account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clone the repo &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/zype/zype-roku&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have the code on your computer, you will need to do 3 things to customize the Roku app
for your own app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, you need to open the app.mk file and set the ROKU_DEV_TARGET to your Roku Player’s IP
address and set the DEVPASSWORD to your Developer Password.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, you will need to change the hard coded keys/initialization variables that are
located in source/objects/config.brs. You will be able to find your api_key, app_key, and
player_key in the Zype Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third, you need to make sure that the APPNAME in the Makefile matches the name of the Roku App’s directory that you cloned into. If you do not change anything from cloning, the Makefile and the
directory name should both be zype-roku.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, its time to test run your Roku App on your local Roku. Navigate to the Roku app’s directory in your computer’s terminal and run:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ make install&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will build the app onto your local Roku. Once the build is finished, the channel will automatically load. Test to make sure everything works appropriately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that your Roku app is built, you will need to publish the app to the Roku Channel store.
&lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/publish-roku-app/&quot;&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to read how to publish your Roku App.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More tutorials in this series:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part I: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/25/create-roku-app-on-zype/&quot;&gt;Creating a Roku Channel using the Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part III: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/publish-roku-app/&quot;&gt;Publishing the Private Roku Channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 02:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/develop-roku-app-with-zype-sdk</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/develop-roku-app-with-zype-sdk</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Embedding a Video Player Using the Zype Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Zype Platform allows you to manage all of your video content in one place and
then deliver your video content across any platform or device. In this tutorial, I
will map out how to embed a video uploaded to the Zype Platform on any webpage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Navigate to your video’s page and click on the Embed Code tab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/kvfYeCS.png&quot; alt=&quot;Go to Embed Code&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copy the embed code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/yJLyMCp.png&quot; alt=&quot;Copy Embed Code&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Place the div with the id player_id where you want your player to appear on your webpage.
We recommend that video embed codes are included before the closing body tag on your site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot; data-lang=&quot;html&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;div&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;id=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;player_id&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;script &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;type=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;src=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;https://api.zype.com/player.js&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;script &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;type=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;player_key&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;3EytE8rlvjELg7sVXINIcA&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;zype&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;play&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;#player_id&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;5477416869702d6d03150000&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;autoplay&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;kc&quot;&gt;true&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;});&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 02:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/27/embedding-player</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/27/embedding-player</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Publishing a Roku Channel: Part I - Creating a Roku App Using the Zype Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest strengths of the Zype Platfom is its ability to distribute your
video content on multiple platforms like Roku. In this tutorial, we will describe how to use
the Zype Platform to create a Roku app that looks like the screen shot below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/d15uKlK.png&quot; alt=&quot;Roku Home&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upload your videos into the Zype Platform. Roku will only serve videos from the Zype
video source. Don’t worry if you have videos from other sources like Hulu and YouTube.
The Zype API can query to only show Zype Videos in your Roku App.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Y6ozC6J.png&quot; alt=&quot;Video Catalogue&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Navigate to the Video Apps screen using the left hand navigation and click on the Roku
icon to start the process of creating a new Roku App.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/77nsysj.png&quot; alt=&quot;Select App&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be prompted to answer questions about how you want to set up your Roku App.
Don’t worry if you want to change these configurations down the road.
The Zype Platform and API are designed so that these changes can be updated without having to republish your app!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, you can set the featured playlist, the category to iterate through, copy text, and
the colors of your Roku App any time you want from the Zype Platform. These changes will be reflected the
next time your Roku App is loaded. Only the Splash Screen and the Roku Store Icons cannot
be updated via the Zype Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/gkeHiEI.png&quot; alt=&quot;New Roku App&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you create your Roku App, you will need to publish the App on the Zype Platform
by clicking on the Publish App button so that your App’s API goes live.
Then, you can use our API, Roku SDK, or reach out to Zype to help you build and publish the App on the Roku Channel Store!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More tutorials in this series:&lt;/strong&gt;
Part II: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/develop-roku-app-with-zype-sdk/&quot;&gt;Developing the Roku Channel using the Zype SDK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part III: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/publish-roku-app/&quot;&gt;Publishing the Private Roku Channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 02:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/25/create-roku-app-on-zype</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/25/create-roku-app-on-zype</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Uploading Videos With the Zype Command Line Interface</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re rolling out a bunch of new ways to add video content to the Zype Platform, like &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/18/search-youtube-in-zype/&quot;&gt;Youtube Channel Import&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/19/adding-crunchyroll-as-a-video-source/&quot;&gt;Crunchyroll Video Import&lt;/a&gt;. In this post we’ll show you how to use the Zype Command Line Interface (or CLI) to upload videos that you have stored on a harddrive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;downloading-and-installing-the-zype-cli&quot;&gt;Downloading and Installing the Zype CLI&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, you’ll need to download and set up the Zype CLI. You can find the tool on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/edla/zype-cli&quot;&gt;gitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ZC3mLEs.png&quot; alt=&quot;gitHub&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll need to clone down the repo, then run the following commands:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ gem build zype.gemspec
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ gem install ./zype-1.0.0.gem
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can confirm that your installation succeeded by entering&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ zype
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;which will display a list of available commands for the Zype CLI. Remember this command in case you have questions about what the Zype CLI can do!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/YZ8gcJl.png&quot; alt=&quot;CLI Interface&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;logging-in-through-the-zype-cli&quot;&gt;Logging in through the Zype CLI&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s make sure that you can login and that your Zype CLI is linked to your instance of the Zype Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter the command below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ zype account:login
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll be prompted to enter your Zype API Key. You can find this by logging in to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com&quot;&gt;Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt; and clicking on API within the settings menu at the top of the screen. Grab your API key and enter it into the terminal to continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;uploading-your-videos&quot;&gt;Uploading your videos&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll need to know which directory contains the videos you want to upload. Once you know where they live, you can run the upload command.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If all of the files live in a single directory, run the following command, replacing the example directory (“/myDir/videos”) with your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ zype video:upload --directory=&quot;/myDir/videos&quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have multiple subdirectories that contain videos, you can pass in a wildcard character (*) at the end of the parent directory to grab all of the videos within each subdirectory. Like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ zype video:upload --directory=&quot;/myDir/videos/*&quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now sit back while we upload all of your videos and add them to the Zype Platform as video imports. Once we’ve imported all of your videos you will find them under the &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/video_imports&quot;&gt;Video Imports&lt;/a&gt; tab. The last step is to create new videos from the imports or add the video imports to videos you already have on the Zype Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/SrnGXnw.png&quot; alt=&quot;video imports&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;confirm&quot;&gt;Confirm&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can confirm that your videos were added by clicking on the videos tab and searching for the ones you’ve just added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/MHiAOmb.png&quot; alt=&quot;videos&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 02:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/20/uploading-vidoes-with-the-zype-cli</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/20/uploading-vidoes-with-the-zype-cli</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Adding Crunchyroll as a Video Source</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We know you have a lot of video content and we know that you want it all to be available to your viewers through the Zype Platform. That’s why we’re proud to announce that you can now use &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.crunchyroll.com/&quot;&gt;Crunchyroll&lt;/a&gt; as a video source for videos on the Zype Platform!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the announcement, we want to walk you through the setup involved and get you up to speed. If you’ve added videos to the Zype Platform using video sources in the past, the will look very familiar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;navigating-to-the-crunchyroll-video-source-form&quot;&gt;Navigating to the Crunchyroll Video Source form&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, let’s login to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/&quot;&gt;Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt; and go to &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/video_sources&quot;&gt;Video Sources&lt;/a&gt;. Now click on the Crunchyroll icon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/oSJebB6.png&quot; alt=&quot;click crunchyroll&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;adding-your-affiliate-code&quot;&gt;Adding your affiliate code&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter a name for your Crunchyroll Video Source (something you’ll remember!) and your Crunchyroll Affiliate code (this is provided to you by Crunchyroll when you become an affiliate.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/tPG2uZv.png&quot; alt=&quot;add name and affiliate code&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;importing-your-videos&quot;&gt;Importing your videos&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now sit back while we go get all of your Crunchyroll videos and add them to the Zype Platform as video imports.
Once we’ve imported all of your videos you will find them under the &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/video_imports&quot;&gt;Video Imports&lt;/a&gt; tab. The last step is to create new videos from the imports or add the video imports to videos you already have on the Zype Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/SrnGXnw.png&quot; alt=&quot;video imports&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;confirm&quot;&gt;Confirm&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can confirm that your videos were added by clicking on the videos tab and searching for the ones you’ve just added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/MHiAOmb.png&quot; alt=&quot;videos&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 02:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/19/adding-crunchyroll-as-a-video-source</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/19/adding-crunchyroll-as-a-video-source</guid>
        
        
        <category>admins</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Searching For A YouTube Channel in the Zype Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We simplified the process of searching for and importing a YouTube Channel into the Zype Platform.
Before, you had to manually go to YouTube and find your Channel ID. This was a cumbersome
process. Now you can search for a YouTube Channel from the Zype Platform and we will get the Channel ID for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to Video Sources and click on the YouTube icon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/xJoXbpp.png&quot; alt=&quot;click youtube&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter a name for your YouTube Video Source (something to help you remember it!) and click the
Search YouTube Channels button&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Ly24GBg.png&quot; alt=&quot;search youtube channels&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter the channel name that you are searching for and click Search. You will be
given a list of YouTube Channels that match your search criteria. Click the Select Channel
button for the YouTube Channel that you want to add.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/hpAfMu8.png&quot; alt=&quot;click select channel&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will prepopulate the Channel ID for you. All you need to do is click Save Changes
and the Zype Platform will start to import all of the videos from the channel that you selected!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/fszuPQu.png&quot; alt=&quot;click submit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 5:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your imported videos are in your import videos page. You can add videos to your catalogue
from there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ZKliLxG.png&quot; alt=&quot;import videos&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 22:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/17/search-youtube-in-zype</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/17/search-youtube-in-zype</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Annoucing the Zype Glossary!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As you might have seen in previous blog posts, we’re constantly adding new features and improving upon the Zype Platform. It only seemed right to start cataloguing the terms we use for easy lookup. Enter &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/glossary/&quot;&gt;the Zype  Glossary&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve organized terms into groups by topic: General Terms, Video Technology Terms, Zype Platform Terms, and a few others. If you’re ever unsure of what we mean, check the glossary (permalinked on the nav bar) for a simple, straightforward explanation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 18:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/17/announcing-the-glossary</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/17/announcing-the-glossary</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Importing a YouTube Channel to the Zype Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With the Zype Platform, you can import all of the videos within a YouTube Channel.
This tutorial will go over the three steps to importing all the videos within a Youtube
Channel to your Zype video library.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the Video Source page in the Zype Platform, click on new YouTube Video Source&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/JoQNGol.png&quot; alt=&quot;youtube video sources&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add a new Youtube Video Source you need to input your YouTube Channel ID. Input
your YouTube Channel ID and click save changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/n8Qa0E0.png&quot; alt=&quot;youtube video source new&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Need help finding the YouTube Channel ID? &lt;a href=&quot;/posts/2014/11/04/finding-youtube-channel-id/&quot;&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; for
our tutorial on finding the Channel ID.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you click save changes, the Zype Platform will import the YouTube videos in the
channel supplied. You will need to add those videos to your Zype video library from
the import video screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/yU2X3UU.png&quot; alt=&quot;import youtube video&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The video imports that you add will now be a part of your Zype video library.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 02:57:55 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/05/importing-youtube-channel-to-zype</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/05/importing-youtube-channel-to-zype</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
