<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zype Dev Portal</title>
    <description>This is the devloper portal for Zype Media. Zype is Revenue and Reach Magic for Online Video. We help content owners deliver fully branded video experiences.
</description>
    <link>http://dev.zype.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://dev.zype.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 15:59:34 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 15:59:34 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Adding a YouTube Video from a Link</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re happy to announce that the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com&quot;&gt;Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt; now grants you the power to import videos from YouTube simply by copying an pasting a YouTube link into the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com/video_imports&quot;&gt;Video Imports Screen&lt;/a&gt; and click on the “Add a YouTube Video Import” button to get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/4lSzNBt.png&quot; alt=&quot;navigate to form&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next step is to copy a URL from YouTube that shows the video you want to add.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/QdHp2nM.png&quot; alt=&quot;copy url&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paste the URL into the field on this page and click “Add Video Import”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/jtREFxL.png&quot; alt=&quot;paste url&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If everything went according to plan, you should see the video imports screen again, with a new import from the link you provided. If you’re interested in grabbing a bunch of videos from YouTube, you may want to follow our guides under &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/platform_docs/adding_videos/&quot;&gt;Adding Videos.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 21:16:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/25/adding-youtube-embeds</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/25/adding-youtube-embeds</guid>
        
        
        <category>platform</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Filtering Videos and Playlists</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been busy adding video content to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com&quot;&gt;Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt; and creating playlists, you might be at the point where you’ve got a few pages of each. To help you better manage your content, we’ve added a set of filters to the videos and playlists pages:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/BOCwSVG.png&quot; alt=&quot;video filtering&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/CVg7VSJ.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlist filtering&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The filter buttons let you select as many parameters for your search as you’d like. Each button has a dropdown you can use to select a value to search by. The default search options are the categories you’ve created for your site and “Active” (whether or not the video is marked as active). You can create and manage your categories &lt;a href=&quot;https://admin.zype.com/categories&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve selected all of the filters you want to use, click the search button to see the results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can search by entering a search term, using the filters or both!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the filter buttons are greyed out, that’s because you don’t have any videos or playlists yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out our previous blog post on &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/04/defining-categories-and-playlists/&quot;&gt;defining categories and playlists&lt;/a&gt;, if you have questions about getting started.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 07:16:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/10/filtering-videos-and-playlists</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/10/filtering-videos-and-playlists</guid>
        
        
        <category>platform</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Using Embed Codes on Your Site</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re happy to announce that the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com&quot;&gt;Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt; now grants you the power to “grab and go” with embed codes! Each video that you add to the platform has a snippet of code located under the Embed Code tab. You can navigate to the tab by finding a video that you want to embed and clicking on the edit button. The tab appears along the top of the menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/V3LoUYw.png&quot; alt=&quot;embed code&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The embed codes are designed to be dropped into a webpage, wherever you need them. The div id must remain the same, but other than that, you’re free to do as you please. As the page states, we recommend that you include the javascript portion of the embed code before the closing body tag on the page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope you use this feature to get up and running with Zype videos on your site in the blink of an eye!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 23:16:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/07/using-embed-codes</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/07/using-embed-codes</guid>
        
        
        <category>platform</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zobjects in the Zype Platform</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A central component of the Zype Platform is a ‘Zobject.’ A zobject is additional
metadata that you can create and associate with your videos. In the tutorial below,
we will show how to associate an the actor John Boyega to the newest Star Wars trailer.
To do this, we will create a zobject type called actors and then create a zobject actor for John Boyega.
Lastly, we will associate John Boyega with the Star Wars trailer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1: Create a Zobject Type&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since zobjects can be whatever metadata you want, you first need to create a zobject type
to define the your zobject data structure. You can access zobject types using the
settings toolbar at the top of your dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/tlg7ik8.png&quot; alt=&quot;zobject type settings&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will call our zobject type actor so that it is easy to reference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/tEzQf7F.png&quot; alt=&quot;zobject type title&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our actor zobject, we need a field for name, which is a string.
You can use any familiar data structure when creating a zobject type.
You can access zobject types using the settings toolbar at the top of your dashboard. To add an attribute,
click the button Add Attribute. You can always return to this page to add additional
attributes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/DOq76qY.png&quot; alt=&quot;zobject type add attribute&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2: Add an Actor Zobject John Boyega for the Zobject Type Actor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click on your Zobject in the right hand navigation or via the appropriate tile on
the dashboard home screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/kA0xlr7.png&quot; alt=&quot;access zobject&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, click on ‘Add New Actor’. You will be prompted to fill out all the information
that you laid out when you created your zobject type. We have included keyword
and description as additional fields that you can leave blank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/oSewGUE.png&quot; alt=&quot;insert actor info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3: Link the Zobject to the Video&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click on the Videos tab to associate videos with the actor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/mRdieLV.png&quot; alt=&quot;associate videos&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you click save, your zobject will be associated with that video! You can double
check by going to the video and looking at its metadata.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/bkPlwIV.png&quot; alt=&quot;video metadata&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 07:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/04/zobjects-in-the-zype-platform</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/04/zobjects-in-the-zype-platform</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Defining Categories and Playlists</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As you make your way through the &lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com&quot;&gt;Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt;, you might have some
questions about the differences between a playlist and a category. At the end of the day, both
are used to return a set of videos, but they aren’t exactly the same thing. This blog post
will look at categories and playlists and help you better understand how and when to use them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-are-playlists-and-how-do-i-use-them&quot;&gt;What are playlists and how do I use them?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A playlist on the Zype Platform is a collection of videos that you assemble under a title.
Common playlists might include: Trending Videos, Most Popular, Editor’s Choice, etc. Playlists
are great for when you want to create and curate, by hand, a set of videos that might not fall
under a specific category.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-are-categories-and-how-do-i-use-them&quot;&gt;What are categories and how do I use them?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A category on the Zype Platform is a label that you can create and assign to any number of
videos. Common categories for video content might include: Genre, Tag, Type, Season, Series,
 etc. Categories are more generic than playlists and can be mass assigned to videos in your
&lt;a href=&quot;http://admin.zype.com/videos&quot;&gt;Video Library.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;im-using-the-zype-platform-to-create-a-roku-app-whats-the-difference-for-me&quot;&gt;I’m using the Zype Platform to create a Roku app, what’s the difference for me?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roku apps will treat categories and playlists the same, as they are both just a collection of
videos. For an in-depth guide on how to create your Roku App, make sure you check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/03/categories-playlists-zobjects-roku/&quot;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 06:16:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/04/defining-categories-and-playlists</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/04/defining-categories-and-playlists</guid>
        
        
        <category>platform</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zype Assets for a Roku Channel</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Adding image assets to your Roku Channel allow your to make the channel your own!
Using the Zype Platform and Zype API, you will be able to change the majority of
images on the fly without having to republish your app. However, there are a few images
that need to be bundled during installation because they make up your
application icon set. These images live on the Roku Channel store.
This tutorial will describe the images that need to be bundled, the images that can
be updated via the Zype Platform, and the specs for both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assets that can only be configured during publication:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example assets are included in our &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/zype/zype-roku/tree/master/images&quot;&gt;Roku SDK&lt;/a&gt; and
need to be packaged with the Roku Channel are because they make up your application
icon set. They do not get loaded via a call to the Zype API:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/zype/zype-roku/blob/master/images/mm_icon_focus_hd.png&quot;&gt;Image Home (Center Focus Icon)&lt;/a&gt; - your large icon. HD is 366 x 210 pixels, SD is 248 x 140 pixels. PNG format.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/zype/zype-roku/blob/master/images/mm_icon_side_hd.png&quot;&gt;Image Brand (Side Icon)&lt;/a&gt; - your small icon. HD is 108 x 69 pixels, SD is 80 x 46 pixels. PNG format.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/zype/zype-roku/blob/master/images/splash_screen_hd.png&quot;&gt;Image Splash&lt;/a&gt; - the splash screen (what appears while your Roku Channel loads).
HD is 1280 x 720 pixels, SD is  720 x 480 pixels. JPG format.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When publishing, you will also need a HD Poster that is a 290 x 218 JPG format and
an SD Poster that is a 214 x 144 JPG format. We call that the Image Store in our Zype Roku App.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assets that can be changed using the Zype Platform and Zype API:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These assets get loaded via a call to the Zype API everytime the Roku Channel gets loaded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/1Cqh522.png&quot; alt=&quot;zype roku app&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/lpgb3MY.png&quot; alt=&quot;zype roku app&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Logo - logo used in the overhang. Suggested size is 125 x 104 pixels, PNG format.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Slice - image tiled to create the overhang. Suggested size is 1 x 165 pixels, PNG format.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Grid Description Image - image used to contain text on the grid screen. Suggested size is 968 x 258 pixels, PNG format.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Grid Border Image - image used for the highlight border on the grid screen. Suggested size is 268 x 190 pixels, PNG format.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Info Poster - image used to link to the info page. Suggested size is 266 x 150 pixels, PNG format.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Search Poster - image used to link to the search page. Suggested size is 266 x 150 pixels, PNG format.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 07:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/03/zype-roku-assets</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/03/zype-roku-assets</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Playlists, Categories, and Zobjects on Roku</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We aim to make the development process of a Roku Channel as easy as possible using
our &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/zype/zype-roku&quot;&gt;Zype Roku SDK&lt;/a&gt;. To do this, our sample Roku Channel
focuses on three major components of the Zype Platform: playlists, categories, and zobjects.
Since the playlists, categories, and zobjects are being pulled into your Roku channel
using the Zype API, they are all editable using the Zype Platform and do not require
republishing to the Roku Channel Store to make a change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be using screenshots from our sample Roku Channel to highlight what you can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/VVuBjU4.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlists and categories&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Featured Playlist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first slider of the home screen is the featured playlist. This can be any playlist
that you have created using the Zype Platform. Note, only Zype Videos will play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Categories&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below the first slider are category sliders. Note that the category sliders and the featured playlist slider are identical.
The only difference is how we are calling the Zype API to return us the videos in each slider.
On the Zype Platform, you select a category that you want to iterate through for the rest
of the home screen. In the picture above, we are iterating through the category ‘Genre.’
Thus, the first category slider is the ‘Genre’ with a value of ‘Adventure’ and the second
category slider will be the next ‘Genre’, which is ‘Comedy’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zobjects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/gS2W1Em.png&quot; alt=&quot;Zobjects in video detail&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You also have the option to provide additional metadata about your videos in the video
detail screen. You select one zobject to be above the description and one zobject to be
below the description. In the example above, we selected the Zobject ‘Actor’ to be above the description
and it lists the actors that we have associated with the video. Similarly, we selected
the Zobject ‘Director’ to be below the description.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 05:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/03/categories-playlists-zobjects-roku</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/03/categories-playlists-zobjects-roku</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Accessing your API and Player Keys</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;To interact with the Zype API, you will need your API Key and Player Key. This
tutorial will show you how to find these keys from the Zype Platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click the settings icon in the top navbar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/MZmuINU.png&quot; alt=&quot;click settings&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the dropdown, select API&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/6CIjtZG.png&quot; alt=&quot;select API&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be directed to the API credentials page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/x3W3bYG.png&quot; alt=&quot;api player keys&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 07:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/01/api-keys</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/12/01/api-keys</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sample Rails App using the Zype Platform and API</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We want to make the Zype Platform accessible to as many types of developers as possible. To do this,
we have provided &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/api_docs/intro/&quot;&gt;API documentation&lt;/a&gt; and are happy
to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:contact@zypemedia.com&quot;&gt;talk with you&lt;/a&gt; about creating a turnkey app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a developer, I always like to learn by example, so we have created
a template Rails app to show you what you can do with the Zype Platform using our Ruby Gem and also provide you with a starter template if you want to build off of it for your own web app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We intentionally kept the styling simple and used &lt;a href=&quot;http://getbootstrap.com/&quot;&gt;Bootstrap&lt;/a&gt; if
you would like to use this example as a foundation to your Rails app.
Feel free to clone the repo &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/zype/zype-rails&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. You will
need your Zype API and Player Keys from the Zype Platform. The README has directions
to how you can find your keys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Zype Rails Sample App has the following pages and features.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home Page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The homepage includes all of your playlists, a link in the header to view all videos,
and a search box to search for a specific video. The Playlists can be configured
in the Zype Platform and can be fetched via the Ruby Gem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/XdD1n7n.png&quot; alt=&quot;homepage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Playlist Page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can click on any playlist to view all the videos that belong to that playlist. You can sort
the videos based on release date, name, or popularity. Also note that there are Zype Videos
and YouTube videos in the same player. The Zype Platform and Zype API allows you to
seamlessly combine the two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/uDlDPcK.png&quot; alt=&quot;playlist page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browse all Videos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The browse all videos uses the Ruby Gem to query the Zype API to get all the videos.
When you hover over a video, you will see the description. Feel free to read the &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/api_docs/videos/&quot;&gt;Video API Documentation&lt;/a&gt; to see what other information
gtes returned when you query for the videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ys7ZfD3.png&quot; alt=&quot;browse videos&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video Page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you click on a video’s thumbnail, you get directed to the video’s page. The video’s page
contains the title, description, and video player. The Zype API will deliver the appropriate
player based on where the video source comes from and what Player Rules you set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/EjY7wlU.png&quot; alt=&quot;video page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have questions about implementing our sample Rails app or want to see examples of
other features or in other languages? Feel free to comment below!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 07:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/29/sample-rails-zype</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/29/sample-rails-zype</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Publishing a Roku Channel: Part III - Publishing the Channel</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/develop-roku-app-with-zype-sdk/&quot;&gt;part two&lt;/a&gt; of publishing a Roku Channel, we described how to develop a Roku app using the Zype SDK and running it locally.
In this tutorial, we will walk through how to publish a Private Roku Channel that you can
share immediately with anyone that owns a Roku. If you are interested in publishing a Public Roku Channel, the steps are very similar, just you have to wait for Roku to approve your channel before it can be accessed in the Roku Channel Store. It is recommended that you first publish a private channel, test the channel out to beta users, and then publish the channel publicly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before starting this tutorial, we will assume that you have already tested a Roku App
locally and are a registered Roku developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Log into your Roku developer account and click Manage My Channels&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/K66GKpz.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click add Private Channel. If you want to publish a Public Channel, click add Public Channel.
The steps are the same for private and public channels, except that you will need to
give contact information in case Roku has questions when they are reviewing your app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/GeJiK58.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fill out Channel Properties for your channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/VZDUXsL.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fill our Channel Descriptions for your channel. You will need to have an HD Poster
that is a 290 x 218 JPEG file and an SD Poster that is a 214 x 144 JPEG file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/pFA3aHQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 4&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can optionally upload screenshots of your Roku Channel. Read the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sdkdocs.roku.com/display/sdkdoc/Channel+Packaging+And+Publishing#ChannelPackagingAndPublishing-38GeneratingScreenshotsSincev31onRoku1andv43onRoku2&quot;&gt;Roku documentation&lt;/a&gt; on how to generate a screenshot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/lMtmsak.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 5&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 6&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last, you will need to upload your application package. Follow the instructions from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sdkdocs.roku.com/display/sdkdoc/Channel+Packaging+And+Publishing#ChannelPackagingAndPublishing-30PackagingYourApplication&quot;&gt;Roku documentation&lt;/a&gt; on how to generate a key and then package your channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have downloaded your Roku Channel package, upload the application package and click the “Publish” arrow. You will get an access code url that can be used to download the private
Roku channel on your individual Roku account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/xufsqQC.png&quot; alt=&quot;step 6&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More tutorials in this series:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part I: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/25/create-roku-app-on-zype/&quot;&gt;Creating a Roku Channel using the Zype Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part II: &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/develop-roku-app-with-zype-sdk/&quot;&gt;Developing the Roku Channel using the Zype SDK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 07:37:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/publish-roku-app</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dev.zype.com/posts/2014/11/28/publish-roku-app</guid>
        
        
        <category>developers</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
